GANNAVARAPU SAI ADITYA

Machine Learning Fellow Fellowship.Al Bangalore, India Phone: +91 - 7032523251

Website GitHub LinkedIn adityagannavarapu.67@gmail.com

PROJECTS

Drawing with Machines, implementing Sketch RNN (Link)

Implemented using p5.js and sketch_rnn.js of Magenta, an open source research project exploring the role of machine learning as a tool in the creative process. Sketch RNN is trained on Quick Draw! doodle dataset of Google. It is generative model for vector drawings. If you start a drawing, it will finish it for you.

Gesture Pong, Gesture Controlled Pong game using Tensorflow.js and Object Detection API (Link)

Using TensorFlow Object detection API, created a game which can be controlled using the gestures of your hand from video in front of webcam. Wave your hand in front of webcam to control the paddle. Inspired from the implementation of <u>Victor Dibia</u>.

3D visualization of Furniture using three.js, deployed to Heroku (Link)

This is an e-commerce store which can help the user to visualize furniture in 3D using three.js. Laravel, PHP and POSTGRESQL for backend. three.js was used to visualize the 3D model in different ways and add different fabrics to the existing model.

Login/Registration SPA, Vue-Firebase application (GitHub)

Implemented an authentication system with real-time DB using Firebase. Built using Vue.js, Firebase, vue-router for routing, Vuetify for material design UI and vuex for state management.

Patient Gateway (Django/ React) (GitHub)

Application built on Django (including the Django REST Framework for API CRUD operations) and React.to view patients and their cancer samples for better prediction of diagnosis for doctors.

Robot Simulation (GitHub)

Application that simulates a simple robot movement and direction using specific buttons in the interface or keyboard. Implemented using React, in process to implement in Vue.

Image Style Transfer using TensorFlow.js (Website)

This is an implementation of Neural Artistic Style Transfer running in browser using Tensorflow.js. This was inspired by the research paper <u>A Neural Algorithm of Artistic Style</u>. Converted the trained model to javascript using tensorflow.js and used it for running in a browser.

For more projects, please visit my personal website or Codepen profile.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE			
Sep, 2019 - Dec, 2019	ML Fellow, Fellowship.AI As a Machine Learning Fellow, I'm working on developing an interface solution for fire hazard problem, which classifies scenes from a given video/image input into classes of hazard or non-hazard.		
July, 2018 - August, 2019	Specialist Programmer, Infosys I was a full-stack developer working on Angular, React, Redux and .NET in an agile process. I was the front-end lead for a team of three working on developing enterprise web applications. Active participant in AI track of Infosys, conducting hackathons and presenting papers on AI, Machine Learning.		
Aug - Nov, 2016	Full-Stack Developer Intern, Third Dimension. Worked as a Full-Stack Developer in developing an e-commerce furniture website which uses Laravel, a PHP framework and POSTGRESQL in the back-end.		
2016 - 2017 2015 - 2016	Technical Secretary, MNIT SPORTS FESTIVAL, Annual Sports Fest. Consecutively held this position for two years. Designed and Developed the website of MST, a responsive, mobile-friendly and dynamic website.		

EDUCATION			
2014-18	Graduation, Electrical Engineering Malaviya National Institute of Technology, Jaipur	(On a scale of 10) 5.27	
2012-14	Intermediate/+2 (Senior Secondary Education) Board of Intermediate Education Andhra Pradesh	95.4%	
2011-12	Matriculation (Central Board of Secondary Education)	(On a scale of 10) 9.8	

SKILL SET AND INTERESTS

- Programming Languages C, C++, Python, JavaScript, PHP.
- Front-End Web Development involving HTML, CSS, jQuery, Angular, React, Vue
- Back-End Development involving .NET, PHP, Ruby on Rails, SQL, LARAVEL, Docker, Django
- Machine Learning Regression, One-Shot Learning, Deep Learning, K-NN, SVM, Cluster Analysis, NLP, LSTM, GRU RNN, CNN
- Interests in Computer Vision, Reinforcement Learning, Genomics, GAN (General Adversarial Networks)

Courses Completed Andrew NG's Machine Learning Course(Coursera) and Deep Learning Course (deeplearning.ai). Languages English (working proficiency), Hindi (working proficiency), Telugu (Native).

EXTRACURRICULLARS

- Technical Secretary, Electrical Engineering Society(EES), Student Body of Electrical Engineering Department, MNIT Jaipur.
- Web Head, MNIT SPORTS TOURNAMENT-2015, Annual Sports Fest.

PASTIME

Playing Football, Digital Art and Graphic Design